Find a comfortable position, close your eyes, and enter your
level by yourself, using the three -to -one method, followed by
a ten -to -one countdown. down.
I will then come in after that with some positive statements and
affirmations.
Take your time.
Thank you.
it is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed a very healthy
state of being
we will now program effective sensory projection for your
success and program information with the use of mental
projection for your benefit we will establish subjective points
of reference at the creative dimension establishing points of
reference at different levels and different depths our present
project is the creation of your laboratory in a moment I'm going
to count from 10 to 1 when we reach the count of
1 we We will have reached a deeper dimension, another dimension
of mind, a very special depth, the creative dimension where we
can create. 8, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2,
1. One.
You are now at a deeper level of mind.
The creative dimension.
I'm going to count slowly from one to three and at the
count of three I will cause a sound of my fingers. By
that time you will have created a room that will house your
laboratory. laboratory.
1.
Begin creating the room by deciding the size and shape you want.
The ceiling height.
Walls.
Flooring.
Leave your south wall blank.
2. Select colors of your choice 3. It is now an accomplished
fact that you have created a room at this dimension. This room
will be known as your laboratory. In a moment I will count
from 1 to 3. At the count of 3 you will have
created a chair with armrests for your use in your laboratory.
1.
Create a chair with armrests. You may choose any size, color,
and type of chair.
2.
Select the the upholstery of your choice.
Three, it is now an accomplished fact that you have created a
chair you will use when working in your laboratory.
I will count from one to three. By that time, you will
have created a desk.
One, create a desk, the size, width, and color of your choice.
2. Place your desk wherever you wish within your laboratory.
3. It is now an accomplished fact that you have created a
desk to be used in your laboratory.
I will now count from 1 to 3. By that time, you
will have created a clock.
one create a clock the size and shape of your choice to
place it wherever you wish in your laboratory three it is now
an accomplished fact that you have created a clock I will now
count from 1 to 3. By that time you will have created
a perpetual calendar.
1.
Create a calendar that will indicate the year, the month, the
day and the date.
2. A calendar that can indicate any date in the past, present,
or future.
Place it wherever you wish in your laboratory.
3. It is now an accomplished fact that you have created a
perpetual calendar that indicates the past, present, and future.
I will now count from 1 to 3. By that time you
will have created an information system that contains
information of all kinds.
1. Create an information system. Its height, width, depth and
color are your choice.
Place it wherever you wish within your laboratory.
2. This information system contains information that can be used
to solve problems of all kinds.
Problems that existed in the past, exist in the present, and may
exist in the future.
3. It is now an accomplished fact that you have created an
information system that contains information for solving
problems of all kinds
Problems that existed in the past, exist in the present, and may
exist in the future
By that time you will have created tools, instruments,
equipment, chemicals, and medications of all kinds and you will
place them where you wish within your laboratory one create
tools instruments and equipment chemicals and medications of all
kinds two tools instruments and equipment chemicals and
medications that existed in the past
3.
It is now an accomplished fact that you have created tools,
instruments, equipment, chemicals, and medications of all kinds
that have existed in the past, exist in the present, and may
exist in the future.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
dimension you can use as points of reference in the future.
It is now an accomplished fact that you have created a
laboratory and that subjective points of reference have been
established at different levels and different depths of the
creative dimension.
To function at these levels and to use these points of
reference, all you need is to have a sincere desire to solve
problems. your mind will automatically seek out these points of
reference where you will perceive and become aware of
information that you can use to solve such problems and this is
so
every time you function at these levels of the mind you will
receive beneficial effects physically and mentally
you may use these levels of the mind to help yourself physically
and mentally
You may use these levels of the mind to help any human
being who needs help physically and mentally.
you will always use these levels of the mind in a constructive
creative manner for all that is good honest pure clean and
positive and this is so you will continue to strive to take
part in constructive and creative activities to make this a
better world to live in so that when you move on You
shall have left behind a better world for those who follow.
You will consider the whole of humanity, depending on their
ages,
as fathers or mothers, brothers or sisters, sons or daughters.
You are a superior human being. You have greater understanding,
compassion, and patience with others.
In a moment, I'm going to count from 1 to 3 and
cause a sound with my fingers.
At that moment, you will continue to exit this exercise on your
own by counting slowly from 1 to 5. And at the count
of five, you will snap your fingers lightly, open your eyes, and
say, wide awake, feeling fine and healthy, feeling better than
before.
I will now count. One.
Two.
Three. Three, continue to exit this exercise on your own by
counting slowly from one to five, and then at the count of
five, you will snap your fingers lightly, open your eyes and
say, wide awake, feeling fine and healthy, feeling better than
before.
Take your time.
Thank you.